https://tyrolbasin.com/privacy-policy/

Snow Report Buy Online (608) 437-4135InfoHoursActivities & EventsRESTAURANTForms/WaiversSnowthings Gift ShopLodgingJobsContactSafety/COVID-19SlopesSnow ReportTrail MapRacingTB Ski TeamDouble Diamond Race LeagueTB Freeride TeamTyrol Basin ParksSki PatrolLive CamTickets/RentalsLift TicketsSpecialsRentalsSeason PassesIndy PassLessonsGroupsEventsWeddings & Other Private EventsEvent ScheduleTubingBuy Online Info HoursActivities & EventsRESTAURANTForms/WaiversSnowthings Gift ShopLodgingJobsContactSafety/COVID-19Slopes Snow ReportTrail MapRacing TB Ski TeamDouble Diamond Race LeagueTB Freeride TeamTyrol Basin ParksSki PatrolLive CamTickets/Rentals Lift TicketsSpecialsRentalsSeason PassesIndy PassLessonsGroupsEvents Weddings & Other Private EventsEvent ScheduleTubingBuy Online
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policyadmin2018-12-29T13:25:00-06:00THE INTERNET, PRIVACY, TYROLBASIN.COM ONLINEThe Internet contains a wealth of information; unfortunately, it may also contain personal details about you that you don’t want everyone to know. For example, your real name (lots of people on the Internet use aliases, alter egos, or nicknames), street address, phone number, or e-mail address. When you go online, sites you visit may be gathering information about you without your knowledge. At TyrolBasin.com we strive to help our customers protect their privacy while using our services.TyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information.LAST UPDATED: 12/29/18SecurityTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with security:The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our Guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to the servers where our information resides. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information the TyrolBasin.com site can’t ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. TyrolBasin.com operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. TyrolBasin.com has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. The security measures we use include a firewall, encryption, and short web page expiration times.The firewall is a combination of hardware and software that securely separates the Internet from the web servers we use. They are designed to prevent unauthorized access to the wrong web servers.Encryption is used whenever financial information, customer identification and passwords are transmitted between TyrolBasin.com and financial institutions. We use an encryption tool called Pretty Good Privacy (PGP). It scrambles your information into an unreadable format called cyphertext, so that even if a third party were to intercept the message, the data would be unreadable. In addition, we use secure site certificates that provide  SSL encryption for our e-commerce.In addition to the technically driven security measures, we also follow internal privacy procedures. In most cases, our employees will see personal information only in aggregate. Employees see only those data they need to complete your sale. All credit card transactions are handled on separate secure servers. Only authorized employees have access to these servers and your personal information that resides on those servers. Remember to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet café.Information CollectionTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Information Collection:In a few areas on our Web site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, process your order correctly, and personalize your experience. For instance, we want your e-mail address or phone number so that we can contact you if, due to unforeseen circumstances (problem with a sale, etc).From time to time we may ask questions, or we may use data collected for order processing, to better understand our customers’ preferences. This information allows us to improve our products and services, and to offer you specially tailored deals when appropriate. While some of this information is optional, other items (e.g., information required to process an order) are not.We will request information from you when you:-Register as a member or subscriber on TyrolBasin.com website. -Place an order with TyrolBasin.com. -Provide feedback in an online survey. -Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer. -Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list.In each of these instances, we may ask for any of the following types of information: name, e-mail address, phone number, address, customer and preference information, customer ID and password, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If you don’t want to receive promotional material or special offers from us, we ask that you tell us this in the section on communications preferences (opt out by un-checking the appropriate boxes). Please note that in the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to “unsubscribe” to these mailings at any time. Furthermore, if you need to change your profile and/or preferences, due (for instance) to a change of address, you will be able to make the change at any time.If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.With respect to Ad Servers: We do partner with and sometimes have special relationships with ad server companies.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.CookiesTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Cookies:For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).We collect only the domain name or IP address, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, but is NOT shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard — you’ll find them at most major Web sites.TyrolBasin.com has three primary uses for cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the TyrolBasin.com site that our users find valuable. Third, to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart.While these activities depend on the use of a cookie, visitors to the TyrolBasin.com site always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the TyrolBasin.com site will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies.Information UseTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Information Use:-Different information will be used for different purposes. Some personal information is required to process your order. For instance. we need to know your billing information, shipping, etc.-We may also use personal account information to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use and for sharing with affiliates. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information. Your identity is kept anonymous.-Aggregate information may be used to design programs and promotions that we think would be of interest to an identified group of customers. For example, if an analysis of purchase data shows that 30% of our guests are small business owners, we may want to develop a special new program for them to benefit.In addition, we may use the detailed profiles in order to target special offers and promotions more effectively. Knowing more about you allows us to personalize the delivery of site content to you should you wish to receive offers from us. If we decide to use information collected for any purposes other than those identified, we will contact you for your agreement.Benefits of Providing InformationTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with the Benefits of Providing Information:Knowing more about you allows us to personalize the types of information we send to you. This means that you will probably receive less mail from us (unless of course you tell us you want everything), and what you do receive will be meaningful and not filled with a whole lot of information that does not apply to you.Non-Use and DisclosureTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Non-Use and Disclosure:We do not and will not sell or rent users information to any entity outside of TyrolBasin.com.Please remember that anything posted on our message boards becomes public information and you should exercise caution about disclosing personal information on those pages.TyrolBasin.com reserve the right to cooperate with local, provincial, federal, and international officials in any investigation requiring either personal information (including any information provided on-line through TyrolBasin.com) or reports about lawful of unlawful user activity on this site.TyrolBasin.com reserve the right to disclose any information in an individual’s account: To satisfy any law, regulation, or government request. If such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to site operation. To protect the rights or property of TyrolBasin.com and its users, sponsors, partners, providers, licensers, or merchants. TyrolBasin.com also reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.Changing Profile and Opting OutTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Changing Profile and Opting Out:Should you not want to receive promotional material from us we ask that you tell us in the section on communications preferences (opt out by un-checking the appropriate boxes).We will also delete your name from the database upon your written request sent to us via email. When you register, and your account is created, we will confirm your registration by sending an email to the address that you supplied to us. All future emails to your account will contain information on how to delete your name from our database. Please keep this email and follow the instructions exactly when requesting that your name be deleted from our database.Contacting CustomersTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Contacting Customers:TyrolBasin.com reserve the right to decide if they will contact customers should we be required to disclose any personal information (as outlined in non-use and disclosure).Photography & ContentTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Photography & Content:All photography and written content is the property of TyrolBasin.com and cannot be duplicated or used for other promotional purposes without the written consent of TyrolBasin.com.Legal LiabilityTyrolBasin.com is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with Legal Liability:Under no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall TyrolBasin.com be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, loss of data or profit, arising out of the use, or the inability to use, the materials on this site, even if TyrolBasin.com or a TyrolBasin.com authorized representative has been advised of the possibility of such damages.Contacting UsIf you have questions about this privacy policy or the practices of this site, please contact: 608-437-4135TyrolBasin.com reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be posted to this page, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you of any significant changes to this privacy policy. However, it is your responsibility to check this site for any such updates as you will be bound by them should you choose to visit our site.  Facebook Twitter Google + Email Newsletter Subscription Email* :
Privacy PolicyRefund Policy  © Copyright 2019 Tyrol Holdings, LLC.
All Rights Reserved
